

CONTACT ME AT

Abc Straße 15
Stadt, Germany

asliyilmaz@yahoo.com

+49 123 456789

in @asliyilmaz

SOFT& TRANSFERABLE SKILLS

• • • • Project Management

• • • • ■ Software Development

• • • • Proactive problem solving

● ● ● ● Conflict resolution

● ● ● ● Adaptability and Flexibility

• • • • Creative & Analytical thinking

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• • • • Data Analysis

• • • • • Data Visualization

• • • • Machine Learning

• • • • Deep Learning

• • • • Python

• • • • • Tableau

• • • • ■ Microsoft SQL Server

• • • • Agile /Jira

• • • • Git/Github

LANGUAGES

English - C2 Level (Proficent)

Germany - B1 Level (Intermediate)

AWARDS RECEIVED

- Most Outstanding Student of Clarusway
 IT Bootcamp, USA February, 2021
- Best Auditing Team Leader, Energy Market Regulatory Authority, Turkey June, 2015

ASLI YILMAZ

DATA ANALYST

SUMMARY

Certified Data Scientist with two years of Data Science experience. Focusing on machine learning, deep learning, and NLP projects. Seeking to contribute to innovative companies and teams. Offering a rare combination of extreme problemsolving, creative thinking, and coding skills. Outstandingly talented at analyzing and understanding a business problem and turning it into a data science problem.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Instructor & Mentor - Data Science (Remote)

Clarusway USA | September 2021 - March 2021

- Training Tableau and leading and reviewing tableau projects.
- Designing Machine Learning projects including real data sets of business scenarios to improve data secience knowledge and experience of students.
- Technical guidance and mentoring students for reviewing projects and exercises and helping with the execution of them.

Team Leader in Auditing Department

Energy Market Regulatory Authority (EMRA), Ministry of Energy (Ankara) | Jan 2013 - Sept 2017

- Led a team of 5 energy experts in different projects.
- Managed complex projects from start to finish
- Instructed assistant energy experts on projects and writing reports.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Middle East Technical University (METU), Turkey

BSc in Industrial Engineering | Sep 1999 - Jun 2005

- Studied project planning, coordination, and ethics
- Worked with various startups on launching new apps and services

Clarusway Data Science Bootcamp, USA

2020 - Feb 2021

- Completed the heavily loaded bootcamp with the highest score, 1st ranking.
- Improved Data Science and Machine Learning skills through application of theoretical infrastructure to 10+ carefully tailored capstone projects.